Pace !Hell Pace !Hell
Pace !Hell Pace
!Hell
Pace!
Paulie Paulie Nobunaku ka i shi o mochi
Tunaateva Toki no
Iito ga ipadunakaru
Dorry Daddy to Call ni sekai kahwaritukete
What?! The Dr. Vegapunk? Really?
Scream about it, why don't you?
I'm your biggest fan!
I can't believe this!
I've wanted to meet you for so long!
You taught me so much!
I spent two years at
your lab in Baltimore!
I studied everything I
could get my hands on!
Like everything!
You gotta see the stuff I made!
This is a dream come true!
I can't believe it!
A giant robot!
It's like General Franky,
but a bajillion times bigger!
I wish Luffy and Chopper
were here to see it!
Vegapunk is a total babe!
Can I take a look at your panties, please?
I'm beautiful!
Giant robot!
Super!
Hold on.
Is there something wrong, Robin?
I've never heard that
Vegapunk was a woman.
A young one, no less.
You filthy pirates!
Obviously, I'm not the Stella!
Uh, Stella?
I'm punk too.
Vegapunk Lilith, the evil!
How strange.
Something's off.
Anyway, our budget's
gone down the test tubes.
So hand over your valuables.
Then I'll consider our
business complete. No way!
You expect us to head right
back into that snowstorm?
You saved us from drowning,
so follow through, dammit!
I wasn't trying to save you!
And don't you even think about
trying to sail any further!
I have iron-tight defenses
trained to attack all ships.
Let me introduce you!
I call them...
The sea beast weapons!
Are those guys giant robots too? Sweet!
Okay, now I'm scared again!
Yeah, me too!
Protect me, Robin!
From now on, you play
by my rules or get sunk.
So move it!
Fuck over your treasure!
Okay!
Lilith, what are you doing out there?
Same thing as always, Chaka.
Why are you calling me?
Are you plundering again?
Where is your pride as a scientist?
Pride don't pay the bills
in case you didn't know.
Who is she talking to?
How's the feel from that high horse?
Those are the Straw Hat Pirates.
They're not going to surrender.
Their captain just became
an emperor of the sea.
And sea is for cash!
If I steal from an emperor, think of
all the research funding I can nab!
I'm afraid you've made a miscalculation.
No, I didn't.
I surrounded them with sea beasts.
There's no escape.
Hear that, dimwits?
You're underestimating them.
Look at the swordsman on the ship.
He has a bounty of 1,111,000,000 berries.
That's Pirate Hunter Zoro.
Notice how calm he is?
That's because he knows he can kill
you in an instant from that range.
The same could be said for
Demon Child Nico Robin.
She's standing right behind him.
But there's no way they could win
against this many sea beast weapons They
don't have to the strong can determine
the highest priority target in this case.
That's you So what are those jokes then?
decoys?
Crafty bastards.
Hey Vegapunk.
From now on, you play by our rules.
Or you're sunk!
Is that a threat?
Do you know who you're talking to?
It's fine bring them in so we can speak I
happen to have an interest in that crew.
You said you've been on
this island before, right?
I came here when I was a kid.
It was just a regular lab then.
Why'd you come back?
Must be real important.
You said you had business with Vegapunk?
You're damn right I do.
And if I can't settle it, I'll kill him!
What does that mean?
What did he do wrong?
Years ago, Vegapunk turned
my father into a cyborg.
Whoa, a cyborg? That's so
cool! Shut the hell up!
My father had all sense of
self ripped away from him.
He doesn't even know who he is anymore.
He became nothing more
than a living weapon.
What a horrific fate.
My condolences.
he'll pay mark my words I'm sorry Boggy
I didn't know Bonnie
just keep moving
This should get us to the surface.
Sounds good.
Hey, look!
I can see the exit!
A future island!
All I see in my future
is food, food, food!
This is it! This is it!
Okay, let's find some snacks and...
Yeah, love me!
You see something cool?
Hey, wait for me!
Probably should have told him I
saw Sabo at Marie Joie. Oh well.
This place is crazy!
There's a giant robot!
This is quite a sign.
Is that a space monster?
And look at all the stuff in the sky!
Ha! Awesome!
I'm gonna ride on the red guy!
Luffy, let's be careful!
We need to keep a low profile, stupid!
Get back here! Rocket!
Ah! Ah!
The thing swallowed Luffy!
Oh no, Luffy! Luffy!
Oh, I thought the lizard eat me.
Enjoy your morphine!
Ah!
Body down food!
Fruit and cookies!
Hey!
Come back here!
It could be a trap! Bordeaux! This hurts!
I'm gonna let you eat!
Time to get in!
Why can't I eat this stuff?
I flip off!
You have to go right through it!
Ow!
Let me eat you!
No bear, I'm starving!
This is a nightmare!
I think I figured it out.
What is it?
We can't touch it because we're dead!
You mean we're ghosts?
Wait a minute, Luffy.
Leave it alone, I'm already dead.
That doesn't seem likely to me.
Then why do I go through the food?
I don't think we're the
ones who are immaterial.
Let me try something.
I thought so.
I'm afraid this parfait
is only a hologram.
A hologram?
Why are they messing with me?
I have no idea why they'd want to
litter the streets with fake food.
But I'm not exactly an
expert on holograms.
Well, I hate them! They're
mean! They're not mean.
Their image is produced by light.
Haven't you seen this kind
of stuff in a comic before?
It's sci-fi.
It's a liar!
That must be why I went
straight through that monster!
The giant robot must be a hologram, too.
No one could make one that big.
Guys, look at this!
What is this thing? What?
There's pictures of
food on all the buttons.
It's probably fake like everything else.
Just give it up.
This island sucks.
Something else is
strange about this place.
Just a short while ago,
we were all freezing.
But since we've arrived
here, it's been quite warm.
Well, yeah, that's because I
set the climate to tropical.
Gotta get crafty when you
live on a winter island.
I invented the island AC so
we could stay nice and cozy.
I can control the temperature
of this whole island.
The heat comes from the ground.
Speaking of which, you bastards are new.
Where did you come from?
She's bigger than Kaido!
Anyway, I don't have time to chat, so you
guys stay out of trouble, whoever you are.
I'm on my way to work,
so I'd better hurry.
Step aside, please.
I made you make that fake parfait!
I'm starving to death here!
What's the big idea tricking me like that?
Oh, if you're hungry, I can...
Are you a ball of ham too, huh?!
Oh, hey, I hit her! Is she real?
Am I real?
Oh, I'm real.
Real pissed!
I'm sorry.
She is real!
And she killed Luffy!
This texture, this smell...
A real hamburger with real
fries and a real treat! Finally!
And it's not a hobbleblam!
It's real! Give me it!
Molly!
It's the real deal!
Wait a sec, who made all of this?
It came out of the thing!
You think there's someone in there?
He just hit a button and food popped out!
Then what the hell are we waiting for?
Let's start punching some buttons!
Heck yeah!
Root steak, eggs, and a pork cutlet!
Yellow!
More, more, more!
Let's do desserts! No, pizza!
I know what I want!
Ramen, fried chicken, and a hot dog!
Oh, press them all at once
so they come out faster!
Oh yeah, nice thinking!
Of course, Chopper's a genius!
Flatter doesn't make
me happy, you bastard!
What you want, Team B?
I'll pass. Thank you.
Well, Bonnie, you sure eat a lot.
I said I was hungry, and you're
eating as much as you eat!
I was hungry, too!
Yeah, and I was, too!
Looks like my invention is a big hit.
What am I looking at?
What is that thing?
You're curious, huh?
Behold my auto-cooking machine!
As long as there are enough ingredients,
it can prepare 500
different dishes per minute!
It even has a flip-out leftovers mode!
It's gonna change the world!
Or it would change the world...
if we could mass-produce it!
But no, we don't have the budget
to hire technicians for that!
Same with the island AC!
We could use its temperature technology to
track everyone on the island but we don't
have the money every
damn day i build world
shattering new inventions
and every damn day i
get screwed by budget
cuts if i had the money
i could do anything
even control the weather
the world needs my
technology and i need cash
i'm doing my part why can't they do theirs
It makes me so mad! Huh?
Where's my freak accident?
No way!
She punched a hologram?
I tripped, yeah!
It waffles!
I'm better now!
How did you punch that thing?
I thought everything here was a hologram.
Still curious? Then listen closely.
With these light pressure gloves, I can
do more than just observe holograms.
Hi!
What happens when someone
touches an object?
They perceive it as real, don't they?
So she's not real? No way!
Shall we find out?
Loopy, watch out!
She wasn't real after all.
I don't know what can't kill
me and what can't anymore.
What decides if she's real?
If anything is, that's for
you to determine on your own.
Rigid thinking needs to
become a thing of the past.
That's what I say.
Stop ignoring me!
Perhaps I should have asked
sooner, but who are you?
Me?
Hey, nothing but a humble
genius scientist for hire!
Doctor Vegapunk!
Doctor Vegapunk?
Kobe told me about you!
How come you're a giant kid?
What the hell is this liar talking about?
So what's our next move
here's what we know?
There's only one man with
a mind like Vegapunks.
And a genius like that always has a
full plate of course—he could use some
help with his work—but no one else
can keep up with that thought in mind.
He had an idea: what if he split
himself into six different people?
Those offshoots are called satellites.
The satellites function as.
function as their own individuals.
But at the end of the
day, they're all Vegapunk.
If you weren't the one
telling me, I'd say this
was too insane to be true.
Six geniuses.
This'll be a pain.
So we make our way to Egghead.
We tell them we're returning this.
And once we're in, we
kill all of the Vegapunks.
Yes, but his lab's full
of priceless research.
Let's try to keep the
damage to a They want us
to eliminate the most
useful man in the world.
Does this have something to do with Lucia?
Considering the timing it must.
Lucci, you're a smart boy.
You should know better than
to be nosy about these things.
Listen to her, Lucci.
Trouble for you means
trouble for all of us.
Let it go.
Uh-huh.
It was so good.
Too bad everyone else missed out.
Guess we'll have to eat again.
I can't wait to show
them the food machine.
They're gonna love it for sure.
Well, Sanji might not be too happy.
You sure made a big mess.
And those bellies, they look
like they're about to burst.
I always look like this.
Gotta work, buddy.
Wait, what's your job?
Oh, you know, just violence and stuff.
I'm sorry, what?
Are those robots too?
This place is a lab, isn't it?
My guess is that they're researchers.
There wasn't anyone in town at
first, but now there's a whole crowd.
How odd.
Perhaps they were waiting
to see if we posed a threat.
Their clothes look so heavy.
Aren't they too hot in this weather?
Wait a second.
Where'd Luffy go?
That sounded like Luffy's voice.
What are you doing?
And then I tap back!
Luffy!
What's he doing in there?
Hey, guys!
What do you think?
Do you like it?
I love how this feels.
It looks kind of heavy.
It's actually not at all.
And it's cool inside.
You look quite nice.
I want one.
You got the clothes in there?
Yeah, going in.
Free food and free clothes?
The future is so handy.
I do feel a little sticky
thanks to that seawater.
Welcome.
Please choose your
preferred clothing style.
In that case...
Come back here.
I can quite dress myself, okay? Wow!
He was right.
I'm as light as a feather.
I feel like I'm floating in these shoes.
This is great.
The future.
I'm glad they had something
tropical, too. Oh, yeah.
It was amazing, G-Babe. Thank you.
Hopefully this will help us blend in.
Although, it might be too late for that.
I'm going to go and look for a weapon.
Then I'm going to try to find Vegapunk.
So I'm off.
See you around.
Stay safe out there, Bonnie!
Yeah, good luck!
Wait!
It's Kuma. Really?
He could be in trouble.
Is he looking for us?
Let's go! Huh?
Gotta run for it, guys!
He's definitely coming for us!
Wait!
Can you tell me who we're
running away from and why?
Later, okay?
Damn it, no!
Aggravated theft of food and clothing.
Watch out!
He's gonna fire!
It didn't ask for money!
It worked when I hit it!
That sounds like vandalism to me!
This is crazy!
He's trying to kill us!
The law here is quite harsh.
Looks like he's going all out!
We gotta fight back!
Yes, we may be pirates, but
self-defense is self-defense. Let's go!
I'm sorry, Kuma!
All right, Kuma Kuma!
Stop it!
What's your deal, Bonnie?
He's using lasers on us.
Can I at least hit him?
He's my father.
He's all I've got.
He's the only family I have.
When you said your dad
got turned into a cyborg.
You were talking about Kuma?
This isn't his fault.
So don't hurt my father.
I'm begging you.
Run away, you dummy!
That's a pacifista? Stop!
Bonnie!
Close valve two, quick!
We need cover here!
Here, Duke!
I see something dead ahead!
Turn now!
It's no use, Captain!
We can't escape!
Come out and bite me!
We can't take another hit.
The water pressure's
going to crush the sub.
Captain, you've got to make the call.
Let's surface.
To the northeast, near land.
Fire, Captain.
We're headed for land.
Forward to starboard.
Everyone get ready to fight!
Let's go!
Damn it.
Must be a Devil Fruit power.
We're in their trap. Be careful!
Aye, aye, cutie.
I mean, captain.
If you don't shut your
mouths, I'll gut you!
You're cute when you're mad, too!
Oh, no!
I've been glorified!
Ah!
It's spreading to the entire crew!
Then stay away from the
infected! Oops. Sorry.
It's functioning like
a contagious disease.
How are they changing our sex?
Woo-hoo!
Never mind.
I learned something fighting an emperor.
I can break through this!
You intensify your Haki!
It nullifies devil-proof powers!
We've reached the surface, Captain!
I'm okay!
I did it.
There's no power you can't beat!
We can celebrate when
we've won this fight.
Doc the sub.
We're going ashore.
Aye, aye, sir!
Seems he cured the disease already.
He's worth three billion for a
reason, I suppose. Andy Twig.
As soon as he broke through the illness,
his antibodies spread as
quickly as the contagion.
But it was fun while it lasted.
My feminization disease.
Hmm.
Burgess, I'll move us to the island.
Hell yeah!
Guys, is that mountain moving? No!
There's someone lifting it up!
this is true power thanks
to the strong strong fruit
so what he can just toss around
whole mountains now and how
did he manage to get to the
shore so quickly they're using
Devil Fruit powers teleportation
contagion superhuman strength
They must have gained these by
hunting for specific abilities.
I see where their bounties keep rising.
Now, roam.
Amputate!
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Trafalgar Law!
What is this, Blackbeard?
What do you want from us?
Don't be so cold!
We're both from the worst
generation, aren't we?
Commodore!
Stronger says you're a bit too heavy!
And I agree!
I knew someone would be
coming through here from Wano.
I wasn't sure if it would be you, Straw
Hat, or Kid, but that's fine, I'm not picky.
I can't believe you took
out Kaido and Big Bob.
You turned the whole world upside down.
Feels good, don't it?
I bet you've got a fine
treasure from Kaido, right?
How many rote ponoclyphs do you have now?
I can't wait to find out,
because soon they'll all be mine.
I could say the same to you!
So let's do this!
Winner takes all!
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
Thank you
very
much.